Hello friends, welcome to your free
online help. Today I am going to tell you
how you can insure your
bike and car from ICICI Lombard through CSC.
So for all the information,
watch this video till the end. If
you do subscribe, let's start the video.
First of all, you have to log in
to Digital Seva and you will get the
option of insurance, you have to click on it,
like Yuva and third party. Click on it. If
Yuva does
not appear as such third party part, then you can
delete it by deleting your browser history.
If you do it, you will feel
that you have to click here.
As soon as you click,
this interface will open in front of you. So,
see here the product is visible, motor and
health. So, you have to select motor first. Two
wheeler, car, PVC, two wheeler, third party,
if you want to select it, then you have to
select it here. If you want to do third party, then you have to
select this line. So, let
me show you how to do third
party insurance of two wheeler. So, I will
subscribe you to click on two wheeler. Put the vehicle number here and
then you have to click on it. This association  If you want to
subscribe to this then
you have to register here, here you have to select the registration
date, that is,
you have to select the customer state here,
then you have to select which company's manufacturer
is the bike, then you have to
select the model, you have to select whether
you want to police for one year, for
2 years, for 3 years, here
you have to enter the engine number of the bike, here
you have to enter the chassis number, then you have to confirm whether it is
absolutely correct or not, then
you have to select the body type, if it is
not, then you have to select it,
then you have to
select the manufacturer, then here you have to enter
your individual in the current registration type,
then you have to do nothing if you did not have any driving
license, if you do not have any previous
restricted third party payment then Rs 600 will be
charged for subscribing to insurance, then
you have to keep need additional cover on this and if
Prithvi previous insurance policy
details are available, if it is available then click yes, otherwise click no,
this
is not mandatory, then you  You have to click on graded, it
is looted but here the total premium has come
and the court number has also come, you
can note down the code number, then
if you want to give money then you can give it, otherwise
you have customer details, here you have to
click on create new customer
and here you have to select the title of the customer,
Mr. or whatever it is, then you have to
enter the name of the customer, whatever is given on the RC,
you have to enter the same name, then if you
want, you can select the date of birth of the customer,
but this is not mandatory, then
you have to fill this correspondence address,
here you have to enter the pin code, you have to
select the pin code from the pad, there was a
loot, you have to enter the email ID here, turn it on
and here you have to enter the mobile number of the customer,
then you have to go down and click on get proposal,
then the total
premium will come in front of you, the proposal ID will come and
brother, the option of buy policy of the police will come,
if you want to see for which days the days are getting deducted, then
you can check by clicking on premium breakup  You can do it and then
if you want to buy a policy,
you will click on the insurance policy, then the CSC
wallet page will open in front of you, here you have to
enter your CSC ID and password,
then you have to click on validate
and after that you will be asked for wallet PIN,
here you have to enter the PIN of your AC,
then you have to click on pay, the
processing will take some time, after that this page will appear in
front of you, you have successfully
generated policy, please find details below,
all the details in it, policy number, here
you will see an option, you
can download subscribe and print it and
show it to the customer, so I hope
you liked the video, if you liked this video then
definitely like this video and
definitely share it with your friends.